(The characters, locations, organizations and events in the play are purely fictitious)
( 극중 등장 인물, 장소, 조직, 사건 등은 모두 허구입니다)
Who are you?
누구세요?
How come you have this watch?
왜 이 시계를 갖고 있나요?
I heard that Taihu would die if he messed around with you.
태호가 너한테 장난치면 죽는다고 들었어.
Taihu never said he had a cousin
태호는 사촌이 있다고 말한 적이 없다
Have you found Taihu's murderer?
타이후의 살인자를 찾았나요?
Is this what you came here to ask about?
이게 물어보려고 여기 온 거야?
We are also looking for someone
우리도 누군가를 찾고 있어요
That's enough
충분 해
What did you just say?
너 방금 뭐라고 했어?
Really
정말
Don't do anything
아무것도 하지 마세요
Why do you suddenly want to find Taihu when you have nothing to do?
할 일도 없는데 왜 갑자기 태호를 찾고 싶은 걸까요?
none of your business
네 상관은 없어
What the hell are you doing?
당신은 뭐 해요?
My friend died
내 친구가 죽었어
Just looking at you bunch of losers makes me angry.
너희 패배자들을 보는 것만으로도 화가 난다.
Goddamn
젠장
how?
어떻게?
Are you really Taihu’s friends?
당신들은 정말 태호의 친구인가요?
Yes or no?
예 혹은 아니오?
What else are you scum doing?
너 또 뭐하는 쓰레기야?
Is it right?
맞아?
where are you going?
어디 가세요?
Of course we are looking for the bastard who killed Taihu.
물론 우리는 태호를 죽인 놈을 찾고 있다.
Then what?
그리고 뭐?
Cut him into pieces
그를 조각조각 자르세요
Come to my office another day
다른 날 내 사무실로 오세요
Let’s talk about Taihu
타이후에 대해 이야기해보자
go away
저리 가요
Do you really want to let him go like this?
정말 그 사람을 이대로 보내주고 싶나요?
How about it?
어때요?
He asked me to go to his office
그 사람이 나한테 자기 사무실로 가자고 했어
Yeah?
응?
I acted very well
연기 참 잘했는데
Fool
바보
"Evil of Evils"
"악 중의 악"
I went to see Taihu last week
지난주에 태호를 만나러 갔어요
The new tower is well maintained
새 타워는 잘 관리되어 있습니다
makes me very happy
나를 매우 행복하게 해준다
correct
옳은
Why didn't Taihu mention that he had a cousin?
태호는 왜 자신에게 사촌이 있다는 사실을 언급하지 않았나요?
Why don't you keep your gold watch?
금시계를 간직하는 게 어때요?
What should I do with a gold retention watch?
금 보유 시계는 어떻게 해야 합니까?
I didn’t see half of their photos together
함께 찍은 사진의 절반도 못 봤어요
Chenghao…
청하오…
There was no news about him after he went to work as a fisherman.
그가 어부로 일하러 나간 뒤에는 그에 대한 소식이 없었다.
He recently came back and asked me about Taihu
그 사람이 최근에 다시 와서 태호에 대해 물었어요.
My brother lives in Wonju
내 동생은 원주에 산다
When Taihu was in primary school
태호가 초등학교 시절
Every summer, I go to Wonju to find Chenghao.
매년 여름이면 청하오를 찾기 위해 원주에 갑니다.
They stick together all day like twins
하루종일 쌍둥이처럼 붙어있네
It is conceivable
그것은 상상할 수 있다
How shocked was he when he heard the news of Taihu's death?
태호의 사망 소식을 들었을 때 그는 얼마나 충격을 받았습니까?
(Anti-Narcotics Division Shi Daoheng)
(마약방지부 스다오헝)
I haven't used half of the money you gave me.
나는 당신이 준 돈의 절반도 사용하지 않았습니다.
Take the money and leave
돈 받고 나가세요
besides…
게다가…
Don't come back again
다시는 돌아오지 마세요
When I see you, I think of Taihu
널 보면 태호가 생각나
will make me hate you
내가 당신을 미워하게 만들 거예요
The variable in the mission is that they may find Taihu's father
미션의 변수는 태호의 아버지를 찾을 수도 있다는 점이다.
Ask me something
나에게 무엇이든 물어보세요
Please get ready
준비해주세요
(Karaoke bar, massage)
(노래방, 마사지)
(Zheng Qitie)
(정 치티에)
Those little punks
그 작은 새끼들
Hello
안녕하세요
Don't just stand, come and sit
서있지 말고 와서 앉으세요
I am always thinking
나는 항상 생각하고 있다
A cousin with whom I had no contact suddenly appeared
연락도 없던 사촌동생이 갑자기 나타나서
Noisy restaurant
시끄러운 식당
What do you think the situation is?
상황이 어떤 것 같나요?
I see through your intentions
나는 당신의 의도를 간파합니다
take it
가져
Stop using his name to scam money.
돈을 사기 위해 그의 이름을 사용하지 마십시오.
Even if you are his cousin, my patience has limits
사촌이라 해도 내 인내심에는 한계가 있어
Take the money and get out
돈을 받고 나가세요
You scumbags are really just hooligans
너네 쓰레기들은 정말 훌리건일 뿐이야
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
Do you think
당신은 생각합니까?
Will I be happy if I just take the money and leave?
돈만 받고 떠나면 행복할까요?
Son of a bitch
개자식아
do not get excited
흥분하지 마세요
I can't stand it, come here
못 참겠어 이리 와봐
-Please... -How?
- 제발... - 어떻게요?
You can't stand it? Come if you have the guts
참을 수 없나요? 용기 있으면 오세요
Want to know what happens next?
다음에 무슨 일이 일어나는지 알고 싶으십니까?
Fuck you, second-rate gangster.
엿 먹어라, 이류 갱스터.
Real or fake, are you blocking me again?
진짜인지 가짜인지 또 날 막고 있는 거야?
Go away, asshole
가버려, 개자식아
Don't do it all, idiot
다 하지마, 바보야
We are not punks
우리는 펑크가 아니다
Longda
롱다
yes
예
go to hell
지옥 에나 가라
Son of a bitch
개자식아
hateful
증오스러운
Damn thing
빌어 먹을 일
Everyone clean up
모두들 청소하세요
yes
예
What are you talking about?
무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
Who kicked me just now?
지금 누가 나를 걷어찼나요?
asshole
항문
come down
내려와
Kick you to death
발로 차서 죽여라
Son of a bitch
개자식아
Flesh feet
살 발
useless waste
쓸모없는 낭비
asshole
항문
Damn it
젠장
Go to hell
지옥 에나 가라
Let me go, asshole
날 놔줘, 이 새끼야
Damn thing
빌어 먹을 일
scrap material
스크랩 재료
you this…
너 이거…
little waste
약간의 낭비
enough
충분한
I don’t think you’re here to cheat money.
내 생각엔 당신이 돈을 속이려고 여기 온 것 같지는 않아요.
Son of a bitch
개자식아
listen to me
내 말 좀 들어봐
When my uncle helped me put on Taihu’s watch,
삼촌이 내가 태호의 시계를 차는 것을 도와주었을 때,
Do you know what he said?
그가 무슨 말을 했는지 아시나요?
He said wearing this watch feels like Taihu is with him
그는 이 시계를 착용하면 태호가 그와 함께 있는 것 같다고 말했습니다.
don't take revenge
복수하지 마세요
But you know what?
하지만 그거 알아요?
Thank you Taihu for treating you as friends
친구처럼 대해준 타이후 고마워요
I really feel sorry for him
그 사람이 정말 안타깝다.
I…
나…
He will avenge Taihu at all costs
그는 무슨 수를 써서라도 태호의 복수를 하리라
You guys are a bunch of bastards
너희들은 개자식들이다.
Just clean this place and stay here
그냥 여기 청소하고 여기 있어라
I will find the murderer
살인자를 찾아내겠어
bring his head
그의 머리를 가져오다
A bunch of unloyal bastards
불성실한 놈들의 집단
His name is Quan Chenghao?
그 사람 이름이 콴청하오야?
Yes, how?
예 어떻게?
Do you want to join him?
그와 합류하고 싶나요?
Just treat it as the reincarnation of Taihu
그냥 태호의 환생으로 여겨주세요
What are you talking about?
무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
You also saw that he is good at fighting.
당신도 그가 싸움을 잘한다는 것을 알았습니다.
One more person like Brother Xu
Xu 형제 같은 사람이 한 명 더 있습니다.
Wouldn’t it be nice to have a strong thug?
강한 깡패가 있으면 좋지 않을까요?
How can you trust him?
어떻게 그를 믿을 수 있나요?
He said he was Taihu’s cousin
자기가 태호의 사촌이라고 하더군요
Nishinari
Nishinari
When did you trust people so easily?
언제 그렇게 쉽게 사람을 믿었나요?
Stop making trouble
문제를 일으키지 마세요
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
you know what I mean
내 말 무슨 뜻인지 알지?
Our business is not simple
우리 사업은 단순하지 않다
It's better to be careful
조심하시는 게 좋을 것 같아요
Stop being so brainless
너무 멍청한 짓은 그만둬
No matter how big or small the guy is
그 사람이 크든 작든 상관없이
You love to pick on me lately
요즘 나한테 욕하는 걸 좋아하잖아
Otherwise, what else is there to find? damn it
그렇지 않으면 무엇을 더 찾을 수 있습니까? 젠장
damn it?
젠장?
Go do something quickly
빨리 가서 뭐라도 해라
Okay, whatever you want to do
알았어, 하고 싶은 대로 해
Hello, have you seen this person?
안녕하세요, 이 사람 본 적 있나요?
-Hello
-안녕하세요
Have you ever seen…
혹시 본 적 있나요…
Wasn't it great yesterday? Super cool
어제 정말 좋지 않았나요? 정말 멋지다
yesterday…
어제…
how?
어떻게?
Isn’t that Quan Chenghao?
콴청하오 아닌가요?
That bastard
그 새끼
-what? Don't pull me - forget it
-무엇? 날 당기지 마세요 - 잊어버리세요
follow me
나를 따라와
-Boss -Hello
-사장님 -안녕하세요
What did he just ask you?
방금 그가 당신에게 무엇을 물었나요?
Ask me if I have ever seen this person
이 사람 본 적 있냐고 물어보세요
(Wanted murder suspect)
(살인용의자 수배)
- Call the police if you see him. - Please give me a bowl of soup.
- 그를 보면 경찰에 신고하세요. - 국 한 그릇 주세요.
-thank you -go
-고마워요 -가세요
goodbye
안녕히 가세요
Hello
안녕하세요
Have you ever seen this person?
이 사람을 본 적이 있나요?
If you see him please call the police
그 사람을 보면 경찰에 신고하세요
That bastard
그 새끼
Please call the police, thank you
경찰에 신고해주세요 감사합니다
(Busan, South Korea)
(대한민국 부산)
- Give it to me - Yes, boss.
- 주세요 - 네, 보스.
very good
매우 좋은
Take it for lunch
점심으로 가져가세요
Thank you boss
감사합니다 보스
Walk
걷다
haven't seen you for a long time
오랫동안 당신을 보지 못했어요
asshole
항문
Son of a bitch
개자식아
Wait a moment
잠깐만요
Calm down and listen to me
진정하고 내 말을 들어보세요
I came here without telling Qi Tie
Qi Tie에게 말하지 않고 여기까지 왔어
I have something important
나한테 중요한 게 있어
I hit it off with you
난 너랑 잘 됐어
I really wish we were friends
우리가 정말 친구였으면 좋겠어
But at that time, classes were clearly defined
하지만 그 당시에는 클래스가 명확하게 정의되어 있었습니다.
I'm talking about you
나는 당신에 대해 이야기하고 있습니다
If you have something to say, say it directly and don't talk in circles.
할 말이 있으면 직접 말하고 서클에서 이야기하지 마십시오.
After listening to this, I will see if I want to stab you with this knife.
이 말을 듣고 나면 이 칼로 당신을 찌르고 싶은지 알아볼 것입니다.
Have you heard the rumors in the world?
세상의 소문을 들어보셨나요?
Is Qitie making a fortune recently?
Qitie는 최근에 큰 돈을 벌고 있나요?
Don't ask around, just fart quickly
묻지 말고 빨리 방귀를 뀌세요
He sends tens of millions in cash to the boss every month
그는 매달 수천만 달러의 현금을 상사에게 보낸다
Think about how much he actually makes
그 사람이 실제로 얼마나 버는지 생각해 보세요.
He will become arrogant after making a little money
그는 돈을 조금 벌면 교만해질 것이다
Now he looks down on people
이제 그는 사람들을 무시한다
Thinking you are superior
당신이 우월하다고 생각하는 것
We have been friends for ten years, and he calls me back and forth
우리는 10년 동안 친구였고 그 사람은 나에게 왔다 갔다 전화를 했습니다.
Poor waste
불량 폐기물
So embarrassing
매우 당황스러운
Han Tu
한투
Let's work together to get rid of Qi Tie
Qi Tie를 없애기 위해 함께 노력합시다
You have a chance to take it back domineeringly
당신은 그것을 횡포하게 되돌릴 기회가 있습니다
previous territory
이전 영토
We discouraged him so he couldn't work
우리는 그가 일을 할 수 없도록 그를 낙담시켰습니다
Take away his business
그의 사업을 빼앗아
I am familiar with all operations
나는 모든 작업에 대해 잘 알고 있습니다.
useless things
쓸모없는 것들
You came all the way to betray your friends?
친구를 배신하려고 여기까지 왔다고?
We didn't have a wedding and my girlfriend is eight months pregnant
우리는 결혼식을 올리지 않았고 내 여자친구는 임신 8개월이에요
I want to support my family, don’t people need to have great ambitions?
나는 가족을 부양하고 싶은데, 사람은 큰 야망을 가질 필요가 없나요?
You can ask the boss first
사장님께 먼저 물어보시면 됩니다
Gather the old Busan gang again
옛 부산 패거리들을 다시 모아라
Then I will take care of the Jiangnan side
그럼 강남쪽은 내가 처리할게
It shouldn't be difficult
어렵지 않아야 해요
To leave a message please press two
메시지를 남기시려면 2번을 눌러주세요
Please leave a message
메시지를 남겨주세요
Yi-jeong, I’m in Daegu
이정아 나 대구야
A murder suspect fled here
살인 용의자가 이곳으로 도주했다
I'm going to stay and watch him until I catch him.
나는 그를 잡을 때까지 머물면서 그를 지켜볼 것이다.
don't worry too much
너무 걱정하지 마세요
I will leave another message
또 메시지 남길게요
Why so slow?
왜 그렇게 느린가요?
Traffic jam on the road
도로의 교통 체증
Pour me a drink
나한테 한잔 부어줘
Please nod, we promise not to fail
고개를 끄덕여주세요 실패하지 않을 것을 약속합니다
We are direct descendants of the gang
우리는 갱단의 직계 후손이다
They are just street gangsters from Jiangnan
그들은 단지 강남의 거리 깡패들일 뿐입니다
There's no need to get angry over a few street gangsters
길거리 깡패 몇 명 때문에 화낼 필요 없어
You are born stupid
당신은 바보로 태어났어요
Or were you being particularly stupid that day?
아니면 그날 특별히 멍청했습니까?
You are your direct descendants, right?
당신은 직계 후손이죠?
Qitie sends me money on time every month
Qitie는 매달 제 시간에 나에게 돈을 보내줍니다.
My Japanese sworn brothers also admire him
나의 일본 의형제도 그를 존경한다
Said no one was allowed to touch him
누구도 그를 건드릴 수 없다고 했어
to be honest
솔직히 말하자면
You take over that area
그 지역을 네가 차지해
It doesn't make much difference to me
나한테는 별 차이가 없어
You know Hong Xicheng, right?
홍시청 아시죠?
He is one of ours now, he will definitely get it done this time
그는 이제 우리 중 하나입니다. 이번에는 확실히 해낼 것입니다.
You let us take over Jiangnan
우리가 Jiangnan을 점령하게 해주세요
We give you twice the money every month
매달 두 배의 돈을 드려요
Zheng Qitie
정 치티에
(Zheng Qitie)
(정 치티에)
I'm Zheng Qitie, come out and meet me
저는 Zheng Qitie입니다. 나와서 만나요
Wasn't there a rock and roll nightclub here before?
전에는 여기에 로큰롤 나이트클럽이 없었나요?
It was left empty when it went bankrupt, and we later took it over.
파산 당시에는 비어 있었고 나중에 우리가 인수했습니다.
Qitie said that this area needs more young people to drive business
Qitie는 이 지역이 사업을 추진하려면 더 많은 젊은이가 필요하다고 말했습니다.
He plans to open a new nightclub
그는 새로운 나이트클럽을 열 계획이다
That stupid DJ really loves to dance and have carnivals
저 멍청한 DJ는 정말 춤추고 카니발 즐기는 걸 좋아해요
Every time you sign a contract
계약할 때마다
It is our tradition to celebrate together
함께 축하하는 것이 우리의 전통입니다
Just tonight
오늘 밤 만
Is everything ready?
모든 것이 준비되었나요?
certainly
틀림없이
Guaranteed to be foolproof
완벽함을 보장합니다
The younger brother hid in three motels
남동생은 모텔 3곳에 숨었다
wait until the time is right
적절한 시간이 될 때까지 기다리세요
They'll rush in in droves
그들은 떼로 몰려들 것이다
To deceive others
남을 속이려고
Only one person can lead a guy, right?
오직 한 사람만이 남자를 이끌 수 있죠?
certainly
틀림없이
Or should I bring the guy in first?
아니면 그 사람을 먼저 데려와야 할까요?
What about hiding them inside?
안에 숨기는 건 어때요?
That's fine if you want
원한다면 괜찮습니다
Listen
듣다
There is a small bar near the stage
무대 근처에 작은 바가 있어요
I'll put the weapons down there
거기에 무기를 내려 놓을 게요
good
좋은
And one more thing
그리고 하나 더
What's up?
무슨 일이야?
They are all my brothers
그 사람들 다 내 형제야
please
제발
Don't be too harsh
너무 가혹하게 말하지 마세요
Don't kill anyone
누구도 죽이지 마세요
What words?
어떤 단어?
That depends on how you arrange it
그건 어떻게 정리하느냐에 따라 다르죠
We have no way to guarantee
우리는 보장할 방법이 없습니다
drive
운전하다
yes
예
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Han Tu, please
한투님, 부탁해요
You've found the right place
올바른 장소를 찾으셨습니다.
What is this place?
이곳은 어디야?
What tricks do you want to play?
어떤 트릭을 사용하고 싶나요?
We're going to party here tonight
우리 오늘 밤 여기서 파티할 거야
In memory of Taihu
태호를 기리며
I don't have time to listen to your nonsense
난 네 말도 안되는 소리를 들을 시간이 없어
carnival?
사육제?
I heard you are looking for Taihu’s murderer
당신이 타이후의 살인자를 찾고 있다고 들었습니다.
Keep the change, please
잔돈을 유지해주세요
join my gang
내 갱단에 합류해
I only opened my mouth because you are Taihu’s cousin.
나는 단지 당신이 태호의 사촌이기 때문에 입을 열었습니다.
Want me to join your gang?
내가 당신의 갱단에 합류하길 원하시나요?
Yeah?
응?
Then who wants to avenge Taihu?
그렇다면 누가 태호의 복수를 하고 싶겠는가?
Let's go
갑시다
Qitie
키티에
who are they?
그들은 누구입니까?
Brother Zhang killed Taihu, those are his people
장 형제가 태호를 죽였습니다. 그들은 그의 백성입니다
Where is the party going?
파티는 어디로 가나요?
That bastard Xicheng
그놈의 서성
Han Tu
한투
damn it
젠장
Seize Qitie
Qitie를 붙잡아라
beat them to death
그들을 때려죽여라
Son of a bitch
개자식아
waste
쓰레기
Get that bastard, you loser
그 놈 잡아라, 이 패배자야
go to hell
지옥 에나 가라
asshole
항문
Who is this brat?
이 새끼는 누구야?
That bastard...get up
그 새끼야...일어나
hurry up
서둘러요
Good night
안녕히 주무세요
Are you annoyed?
짜증나나요?
kill them all
그들 모두를 죽일
Kill
죽이다
Offal
겨
Son of a bitch
개자식아
waste
쓰레기
-I'm going to beat you to death -That's enough
-너를 때려죽이게 할거야 -그만하면 충분해
You choose
당신이 선택
I'm going to die here
난 여기서 죽을거야
Or don't let me see you again?
아니면 다시는 만나지 못하게 하시겠습니까?
tidy up
치우다
I have no strength left, call it a day.
이제 남은 힘이 없습니다. 하루만 기다려 주세요.
Do not touch me
저를 만지지 마세요
Let it go, asshole
놔둬, 이 새끼야
take your hands away
손을 떼세요
Told you not to touch me, you damn bastard
만지지 말라고 했잖아, 이 새끼야
let me go
날 보내줘
Han Tu
한투
- let me go - bastard
- 놔줘 - 개자식
Han Tu
한투
Walk slowly without seeing anyone off
아무도 배웅하지 않고 천천히 걸어가세요
asshole
항문
friend
친구
Get lost, asshole
길을 잃다, 이 새끼야
I see you were beaten badly
심하게 구타당한 걸 보니
Jiangnan is our home
강남은 우리 집이야
Don't come again
다시는 오지마
sorry
죄송합니다
asshole
항문
- Han Tu, he's leaving - bastard
- 한투, 그 사람이 떠난다 - 개자식
Don't come to our territory again, you country bumpkin.
다시는 우리 땅에 오지 마, 이 시골뜨기야.
The blood stains are all gone. Wipe them off quickly.
핏자국이 다 사라졌어요. 빨리 닦아내십시오.
-Jae Hoon -very good
-재훈 - 아주 좋아
- mop it off - good
- 닦아내세요 - 좋아요
- do things quickly - yes
- 일을 빨리 처리하세요 - 예
As expected, you expected it
예상대로 넌 예상했지
They all took the bait
다들 미끼를 물었네
Thanks
감사해요
-Han Tu... -Just asking out of curiosity
-한투... -그저 궁금해서 물어본 것 뿐인데
Why did you call me here?
왜 나를 여기로 부르셨나요?
Force me to fight?
강제로 싸우라고?
Would you like to tell him personally?
그에게 개인적으로 말씀드리고 싶으신가요?
Yes, boss
예 보스
I am Zheng Qitie
저는 정 치티에(Zheng Qitie)입니다
So annoying
너무 짜증나
I heard that you nodded to Brother Zhang’s younger brother
장 형제의 남동생에게 고개를 끄덕였다고 들었습니다.
sneak attack on me
나를 몰래 공격하다
It’s a shame that I gave you so much money
내가 너한테 돈을 너무 많이 줘서 미안해
Isn't this very kind?
정말 친절하지 않나요?
I will never send money there again.
나는 다시는 그곳으로 돈을 보내지 않을 것입니다.
Take care of yourself
몸 조심하세요
Go to Seoul and find Zheng Qitie
서울에 가서 Zheng Qitie를 찾아보세요
Cut open his intestines and throw him into the sea of ​​Incheon
내장을 잘라서 인천바다에 던져버리세요
No, wait
아니, 잠깐만요
Capture him, disembowel him in Busan, disembowel him and throw him into the sea
잡아서 부산에서 배를 풀고 배를 풀어 바다에 던져라
one way or another
어떤 식으로든
Should I contact you?
내가 당신에게 연락해야 할까요?
Kanemoto Rodai?
Kanemoto Rodai?
You must be good at acting
연기를 잘해야 해
Only those bastards in Busan would believe it
부산놈들만 믿겠지
I want to get rid of the useless parasites in the gang
갱단의 쓸모없는 기생충을 없애고 싶다
Just use a trick within a trick
트릭 안에 트릭을 사용하세요.
There's a good reason for everything here
여기에 있는 모든 것에는 그만한 이유가 있습니다
So what?
그래서 뭐?
It's not my business?
내 알 바 아니다?
Where is Brother Zhang?
장 형제님은 어디에 계시나요?
Brother, it's all done
형님, 다 됐어요
Let’s talk after we go out
나가서 얘기하자
yes
예
lit
문학
(Taihu Rock Cafe)
(타이후 록 카페)
Taihu wanted to open a shop here during his lifetime
태호는 평생 이곳에 가게를 열고 싶었습니다.
It should have opened earlier, no one is here now
더 일찍 열었어야 했는데 지금은 아무도 없어요
Too tiger…
너무 호랑이...
like my brother
내 동생처럼
I want you to help him fulfill his last wish
그 사람이 마지막 소원을 이룰 수 있도록 도와줬으면 좋겠어
i killed him
내가 그를 죽였어
That bastard Brother Zhang killed Taihu
그 자식 장 형제가 태호를 죽였어
I chopped him into mincemeat
나는 그를 다진 고기로 잘랐다
My name is Quan Chenghao. Please give me your advice.
내 이름은 콴 청하오(Quan Chenghao)입니다. 조언을 부탁드립니다.
Those who were dissatisfied with him are now wiped out
그에게 불만을 품은 자들은 이제 전멸되었느니라
He is the most junior, so he should be nicer to others, you know?
막내니까 남들한테는 더 친절해야겠죠?
-yes
-예
do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
yes
예
applause
박수 갈채
About Hyeon-dong and Yeoksam-dong
현동, 역삼동 소개
Only these two areas belong to us
이 두 영역만이 우리의 것입니다
Can't cross the line
선을 넘을 수 없어
There is a boss in every district
각 구역마다 보스가 있습니다
The job of the newcomer is to patrol the territory
신입생의 임무는 영토를 순찰하는 것입니다
From five o'clock in the evening to five o'clock the next morning
저녁 5시부터 다음날 아침 5시까지
like a patrolman
순찰대원처럼
Check to see if there are any accidents or if anyone is causing trouble
사고가 발생했는지, 문제를 일으키는 사람이 있는지 확인하세요.
When you see people from other gangs, report it immediately, that's it
다른 갱단 사람들 보면 바로 신고하세요.
Do you understand?
이해했나요?
Turn left over there
저기에서 좌회전하세요
By the way, why are you speaking so politely to me?
그런데 왜 나한테는 그렇게 공손하게 말하는 거야?
I'm very polite to anyone who can fight.
나는 싸울 수 있는 누구에게나 매우 예의바르다.
I've seen your skills
나는 당신의 능력을 보았습니다.
Even Jackie Chan and Bruce Lee have to bow down.
Jackie Chan과 Bruce Lee도 절을 해야 합니다.
You are awesome
당신은 정말 대단해요
Fight well
잘 싸워라
Do you want to learn Taekwondo?
태권도를 배우고 싶나요?
-Are you sick? -Who are you?
-너 아프니? -누구세요?
I have the guts to fight
나는 싸울 용기가 있다
Son of a bitch
개자식아
What's wrong with you?
왜 그래?
Don't be impulsive
충동적으로 행동하지 마세요
Damn thing
빌어 먹을 일
- That bastard - let's go, let's go
- 그 새끼 - 가자, 가자
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
Good night
안녕히 주무세요
Hello boss
안녕하세요 사장님
Long Da, keep up the good work
Long Da, 계속 좋은 일을 하세요
How long will we be patrolling the streets like this?
우리는 언제까지 이렇게 거리를 순찰할 것인가?
We don't have to patrol the streets until new people arrive.
새로운 사람들이 도착할 때까지 거리를 순찰할 필요가 없습니다.
When was that?
그게 언제였나요?
After graduating from high school
고등학교 졸업 후
It will take some time
시간이 좀 걸릴 거예요
Hello
안녕하세요
-Hello, big brother -Longda
-안녕하세요, 형님 -롱다
yes
예
do things well
일을 잘하다
do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
Good night
안녕히 주무세요
it hurts
아파요
If you stay undercover until the end
끝까지 잠복해 있으면
What if driving skills only get better?
운전실력만 좋아진다면?
who knows
누가 알아
I need to take a nap, call me later
나 좀 자야겠어 나중에 전화해
I have to patrol the streets again
다시 거리를 순찰해야 해
Most gangs charge so-called protection fees
대부분의 갱단은 소위 보호 수수료를 청구합니다.
Each of our members runs a store
회원 각자가 매장을 운영하고 있습니다.
Half of the profits are turned over to the company
이익의 절반은 회사에 귀속됩니다.
The system is quite advanced
시스템이 상당히 발전했네요
Do you sell catering or anything else?
케이터링이나 다른 것을 판매합니까?
Something else? what?
다른 것? 무엇?
Gambling or other business
도박 또는 기타 사업
You are the best in the gang, I am the second best
당신은 갱단에서 최고이고 나는 두 번째로 최고입니다
How could I know
내가 어떻게 알아
I only know which nightclub has hot girls
난 어느 나이트클럽에 섹시한 여자가 있는지만 알아
(Seoul Provincial Police Agency, South Korea)
(한국 서울지방경찰청)
(Security Division)
(보안부문)
Mr. Cha Fengzhu
차펑주 씨
If you violate the National Security Law, you will face three to five years in prison.
국가보안법을 위반하면 3~5년 징역형을 받게 된다.
Will be kicked out of university
대학에서 쫓겨날 것이다
You will also have a criminal record when you go out to find a job.
일자리를 찾으러 나갈 때도 범죄 기록이 남게 됩니다.
I do not know anything
나는 아무것도 모른다
I just heard you say you were from Jeonju
방금 전주 출신이라고 들었는데
Me too, I go to Jeonju Girls' High School
나도 전주여자고등학교 다닌다
take it
가져
smoke one
담배 하나를 피우다
Asking a fellow countryman to smoke a cigarette is just a token of appreciation
동포에게 담배 한 대 피우라고 하는 것은 감사의 표시일 뿐이다
I rarely say this
나는 이런 말을 거의 하지 않는다
You know we asked your friends too
우리가 네 친구들한테도 물어봤잖아
Everyone says Bong-joo, you are the boss
다들 봉주야 네가 대장이야
Not true?
사실이 아니다?
Can't you go home and sleep?
집에 가서 자면 안 돼?
Yes, my parents moved to Yishan
네, 부모님은 이산(Yishan)으로 이사 오셨어요
So I have to move out
그래서 이사를 나가야 해요
Then please go take a shower
그럼 가서 샤워하세요
Washed in the morning
아침에 세수함
That was yesterday morning
그건 어제 아침이었어
What the hell, it's still morning anyway
뭐야 아직 아침이잖아
Very hungry
매우 배고프다
Hello
안녕하세요
Is it you who knocks 2473?
2473을 두드린 사람이 바로 당신인가요?
Hello, Yingbi, this is Liu Yizhen.
안녕하세요, Yingbi, 저는 Liu Yizhen입니다.
Junmo's wife
준모의 아내
Yi Zhen, hello
이젠님, 안녕하세요
How is it going?
어떻게 지내요?
I'm fine, thank you for your concern
난 괜찮아요, 걱정해주셔서 감사해요
There is no news about Junmo from yesterday to now
어제부터 현재까지 준모 관련 소식은 없습니다
I'm a little worried
조금 걱정이 되네요
What?
무엇?
What's wrong?
뭐가 문제 야?
He had an asthma attack and called in sick.
그는 천식 발작이 있어서 아프다고 전화했습니다.
So hot
너무 덥다
To listen to the message please click
메시지를 들으시려면 클릭해주세요
Is it me, busy?
나야, 바쁜가?
I know you have asthma, can we still have a meal together, right?
당신이 천식을 앓고 있는 것으로 알고 있는데, 우리 같이 식사할 수 있을까요?
that…
저것…
My friend is in a hurry. I'll go have a meal and come back.
내 친구는 서두르고 있습니다. 가서 밥 먹고 돌아올게요.
It's only a woman
여자뿐이야
It's a woman
여자예요
OK, who is it?
알겠습니다. 누구인가요?
Going on a double date with my girlfriend?
여자친구와 더블데이트를 하러 가시나요?
Handsome ones are the most popular
잘생긴 사람이 제일 인기 많음
I don't eat instant noodles
나는 라면을 먹지 않는다.
Yes, it’s better to eat with a woman
응, 여자랑 먹는 게 더 좋아
I can eat instant noodles alone
라면은 혼자 먹을 수 있어요
Yi Zhen, I'm sorry for not telling you earlier.
이진 씨, 미리 말씀드리지 못해 죄송해요.
Say it now
지금 말해보세요
What are you doing these days?
너 요즘 뭐하니?
Who bought you a suit without letting your wife know?
아내에게 알리지도 않고 양복을 사준 사람이 누구입니까?
you misunderstood
당신은 오해했습니다
To tell you the truth, I want to catch drug smugglers.
사실대로 말하면 마약밀수범을 잡고 싶어요.
Just go undercover and join the gang.
그냥 잠복해서 갱단에 합류하세요.
they really said that
그 사람들이 정말 그렇게 말했어
What a nonsense
말도 안 되는 소리야
Hello
안녕하세요
Chenghao
청하오
-Yes -What are you doing?
-네 -뭐해요?
Just eating with friends
그냥 친구들이랑 먹으면서
Wait, I saw her in high school
잠깐, 나 그 사람 고등학교때 봤어
Didn't expect to see you here
당신을 여기서 볼 줄은 몰랐어요
haven't seen you for a long time
오랫동안 당신을 보지 못했어요
She is my friend from elementary school
그 사람은 내 초등학교 친구야.
We used to learn Taekwondo together
태권도를 같이 배웠어요
Who is this…
누구세요…
I recently joined the company as president
나는 최근에 회사에 사장으로 합류했습니다.
Really?
정말?
Qi Tie is a junior classmate of my high school church.
Qi Tie는 제가 다니는 고등학교 교회의 후배입니다.
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
Very good, thank you for your concern
아주 좋아요, 걱정해주셔서 감사합니다
How are the police doing?
경찰은 어떻게 지내고 있나요?
Did you hear that?
그거 들었어?
Which subject are you in?
당신은 어떤 과목에 속해 있나요?
Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency Security Section
서울지방경찰청 보안과
Have you finished eating?
식사는 다하셨나요?
Finished
완성된
Can I take Chenghao away?
청하오를 데려갈 수 있나요?
I'm leaving. I'll call you later.
나는 떠난다. 나중에 전화 할께.
How dare you meet with the policeman, bastard
감히 경찰관을 만나다니, 이 새끼야.
you misunderstood
당신은 오해했습니다
We have had a good relationship since elementary school
우리는 초등학교 때부터 좋은 관계를 유지해왔어
My dad is a poisonous insect
우리 아빠는 독충이에요
If he takes drugs, he will beat me
그 사람이 약을 먹으면 날 때릴 거야
I used to hide in her house
난 그 사람 집에 숨어있곤 했어
Why are you contacting her, asshole?
왜 그 사람한테 연락하는 거야, 이 새끼야?
Go away
저리 가요
I didn't contact her
나는 그녀에게 연락하지 않았다
It was she who contacted me first
나한테 먼저 연락한 건 그 사람이었어
Why did that female police officer contact you?
그 여자 경찰관이 당신에게 왜 연락한 걸까요?
My dad was caught taking drugs
아빠가 마약을 하다 적발됐어요
Now being held in the police station
지금은 경찰서에서 수감 중
boss
사장
I really do not know
나는 정말로 모른다
You will meet Yi Zhen
당신은 이젠(Yi Zhen)을 만나게 될 것입니다.
Do you have to blame me for this?
이 일에 대해 나를 비난해야 합니까?
Let's go
갑시다
-Chenghao -Yes
-Chenghao -예
Have some respect for the boss, you bastard
상사를 존경해라, 이 새끼야
sorry
죄송합니다
It's me Yi Zhen
나 이젠이야
Do you all know about Jun Mo’s drug investigation case?
모준의 마약수사 사건 다들 알고 계시나요?
Chenghao, do you think I will believe you?
청하오, 내가 당신 말을 믿을 것 같나요?
I hate notes
나는 메모를 싫어한다
enough
충분한
you need to know
넌 알아야 해
A cousin suddenly appeared in Taihu
갑자기 태호에 사촌이 나타났다
His neighbor happens to be…
그의 이웃은 우연히…
Oldest friend from high school church
고등학교 교회의 가장 오랜 친구
Don't you think it's strange?
이상하다고 생각하지 않나요?
South Korea is really small, isn’t it?
한국은 정말 작죠?
Qi Tie, where does she and you like the spicy fried rice cake?
Qi Tie, 그녀와 당신은 어디에서 매운 떡볶이를 좋아합니까?
I think so
그렇게 생각해요
She is his first love, they do everything together
그녀는 그의 첫사랑이고 그들은 모든 것을 함께합니다
It's a necklace given by the high school church.
고등학교 교회에서 주신 목걸이예요.
should take it home
집에 가져가야 해
Subtitle translation: Li Yi
자막 번역: 리이(Li Yi)